Let's see ...
noodles.
bear.
Pan.
Fire everywhere, Marry?
Where do you want to start?
American Ultra.
Well, began three days ago in the city ...
Liman, West Virginia.
Here I live with my girlfriend Phoebe.
She is the only good thing that happened to me.
Honestly I can not remember life before her.
We were a couple, but perfect.
She was perfect, I was the bastard.
And we were very happy.
I wanted to be with me, so save for the perfect ring.
And plan the perfect romantic trip to surprise.
And then I fucked too.
This is the last call for flight 1204 to Hawaii.
I repeat, this is the last call for flight 1204 to Hawaii.
Mike demons.
Welcome to Liman.
I am so sorry.
I thought I could overcome the panic attack this time.
- It's okay. - It is not.
- It's okay. - Not well!
This is something I want to do for you, then I screw ...
and now we're going back home.
- You did not want to. - I did, my fault ...
- You should be mad at me. - Do not!
Why not?
- You can not help it. - Fine thanks.
Oh, hell!
- Have you got something up? - Of course not, we were traveling.
- What for...? - Insurance?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- Hi Phoebe. - Hello.
- Mike. - Hello.
Did not they were going on vacation?
To Hawaii?
Another You had little episode, Mike?
Phoebe know what ...
I want you to take this boy home ...
for not going to panic on the road ...
or leave it in the city.
Is that why we stopped?
Careful how I talk Mrs. Larson.
I'd hate to check the car.
This boy is your boyfriend ...
will begin to brush your teeth every night in the police station.
- Is not it Mike? - This is Sheriff Watts.
Well, I welcome you back to the city.
I pick up the suitcases.
¿Phoebe want to eat?
This could be the right time.
Hey, Mike.
What is this?
Is this okay? I believe-
Phoebe, sorry.
Do you burn your hand?
Do you only let me cook, right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Stop apologizing.
All right.
The Adventures of Chip Ape Apollo and brick.
What did you do to my head?
Level 7.
Gotcha!
I have you!
What are you doing?
Honey, I want to tell you that I have a fun idea for Halloween.
Well, what is it?
HAPPY MONDAY OFFER
OFFER HAPPY TUESDAY
headquarters of the CIA.
How do I read the damn story?
Hello. How are you?
Hello, Lasseter.
You're not my assistant, Petey. What are you doing here?
I know, you just missed.
Come on, you're no longer at the big table, you can let some things go.
Enough, Douglas.
Well, I'm going, you need something ...
Lasseter.
Your program activated tough guys ...
you have to eliminate Howell.
Than?
will take care of it in 24 hours.
This is American soil, they can not do that.
We promised to protect. Who is it?
¿Yates?
The operation is in progress.
You were informed by courtesy.
- Who is it? - Do not interfere, good afternoon .
Then Apollo ape and brick Chip say ...
... What the hell do I go?
They found that Spice was in charge of resistance.
But what they found will know the
next book, the dog is bad asteroid.
- No, man. - I know.
You are a genious.
If you got it is because it is the best friend of man, not the monkey.
Sure, it makes sense to me.
Is dog!
- You should write it. - I do not know, I like to think about it ...
and talk about it.
- The Ape Apollo and his adventures. - I love to tell me about it.
Other people liked it too.
As if they were...
We would love to read it, if you write, really.
You'd be very good at it.
- You know what scares me Phoebe? - Than?
As that car there, it has moved too.
As it was built in a factory, in a production line ...
and then he was shipped here.
And then those guys stolen elsewhere.
Exactly.
But all that time, for years ...
or because I do not know, decades ...
the tree has been in this place as if nothing until tonight ...
to stop the car.
Yes?
So this car is like to leave.
And that tree is always as-
like stopping. Like he was detained for years ...
until tonight when that thing wanted to go and ...
no, you stop too.
The tree has never done anything, it's like ...
destroy this beauty .. Very beautiful and fast moving thing.
- And ... - Why are you crying?
Because Phoebe ...
I am a tree.
Do not.
I think I'm the tree and I think ...
you are the car and I'll stop.
You're not the tree.
It's okay.
I love you.
Phoebe. I'm sorry for what the trip.
Okay, seriously.
And exceeds it. I do not want you to worry.
You do not be so always know?
I am with...
strong and good person I've met in my life.
I love you madly.
- You sneezed on me. - I know.
CIA headquarters.
Yates.
Wait a moment.
- Yes, Victoria? - Should I talk to you now.
Well, we're done here.
Thanks guys.
Stop ignoring me.
I know that guys are after Wiseman above, what happens?
- Where did you hear that? - It is true?
Does not concern you. Yes?
- Wiseman was my boy. - If and more.
- Why are you crying? - You come after my only boy lost?
We finish this in my office.
I do not understand why you're so upset?
- You did not go that closed the program? - Yes, because it was a fluctuating pattern.
For lastimábamos people.
He would not expect me finish and then I kicked his ass.
- And he will take the bones of my operations. - I am now a supervisor.
- The main squad. - What you're temporarily by licking ass.
Because I'm the right man for the job.
Who says it? Does Daffy Duck?
Daffy Duck ...
Well, it seems that I do it well, because I have the job two years ago.
It is assumed that in two months you had to protect troops, not kill them.
- Victoria, clean the dirt. - Than?
Mike Howell tried to stay with the city.
It should be removed.
Are you going to kill him, trying to stay in town?
That is its safety limit. Just I am doing my job.
- I'm doing my job. - It is a human.
You're wrong.
- It's an American citizen. - It is government property.
You know what the fuck are you saying?
- What mouth. - Listen, idiot king.
- If you think I sentaré- - Listen to your ...
tremendous ordinary bank. Howell died today!
And if you can not do anything. What are you going to do?
Are you going to bite?
You're my fucking dog here, okay?
Sit down! Stay!
Turn arround. Now get out ...
my fucking office.
Rose: See you in 15 minutes ?
Mike, what's up?
Swim alone...
I go to work.
Is not it early?
Yes Yes.
But I must do something.
What?
Food.
I love you.
Rose.
What guy?
- How are you? - What guy?
- What's up! - I appreciate you doing this for me.
Come on man, you know I love you, right?
Do I appreciate my black, black, black, you know it?
Yes.
Well, well, go and open the trunk.
- All right. - All right, it's cute.
Very good, quiet, is not a big problem ...
Calm.
Are you ready?
Go Go.
All right.
This is more illegal than what I have normally.
You understand me?
These are expensive fireworks that light up the whole sky.
Rose, Phoebe will love this.
This is perfect Rose is perfect.
Thanks dude.
And tell me this is for a purpose of annihilation you do?
Did you know son?
- That's the plan. - Seems to want your slut.
- I love her. - You must do when you love.
- If you know a friend. - If exactly, it comes once in life.
- That I say. - Yes.
Yes Yes. - Fine thanks.
- You leave? - Yes.
- Where are you going? - I leave it and go to work.
Want something? ¿Foursome drug?
Not well. It is 8:13 is too early for that, Rose.
Thanks Nancy.
Thanks Bryan.
Marry?
Progression attentive, listening ...
the man is on the move ...
has broken the gap, put the ball in play.
That's a guess, or something?
Fuck.
Do not.
Attentive progression, Listen.
According.
- The man is moving. - Ma'am, do you take something?
- Progression attentive Mike! - Lady can stop that please?
- Progression attentive. - Are you OK?
Listen.
The man is moving.
He has broken the gap ...
Progression attentive, careful progression.
Progression attentive.
is in motion. Movement.
- Mike. Please you are in danger ... - Lady is enough ...
- You should listen. - Stop. I must close soon.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
For all this. Sorry Mike, I tried.
All right.
You do not want your soup?
Stop bothering my car.
- What about honey? - I just killed two people.
- Two, I killed. - Sounds great.
These two were trying to steal my car and had guns and knives ...
and they were being idiots and attacked me.
- Honey calm down. - Take a spoon and ...
- Stabs one. - Did you call the police?
I have not called the police because I am the murderer, okay?
And I have marijuana and hallucinogenic mushrooms in my car.
I just killed two guys in the parking lot!
If you do not come now, I'll start to pee in your pants ...
I swear to God I'll Phoebe pee.
How did this happen?
How the hell did this happen?
I shot him in the head.
And that, kind ...
you key spoon in the neck and fell.
- Did you just kill two guys? - They were trying to ...
- Stab Phoebe. - Why they try to do that?
I do not know!
I do not know but...
I'm really scared. By Phoebe what happened here.
I am very anxious about this.
Hands up!
I'm screwed.
What have you done Mike?
I'm sorry.
Throw it!
What do you two low?
We lost two trying to neutralize the cash Howell.
- How is that possible? - I had a spoon Lord.
A damn! ¿Spoon?
Than?
We're not sure why the confrontation but ...
You should activate.
- Did you see that? - Yes sir.
This is Lasseter. She's in town.
Find her.
Closed the bridge, no one enters, no one leaves.
- Yes sir. - Where is Howell, now?
- This arrested sir. - Perfect!
Well, we go in and take it out.
you stuck in one place, you can not get out.
Yes sir!
Use the Frame and Laugher effective.
Except that...
Tell me again to clarify this.
No, no ...
I hit with the spoon.
And they blew their lungs.
What happened to your lungs?
Nothing happened.
Because I could not breathe because I hit in the neck.
- How do you know of the lungs? - What is Phoebe.
No, that does not make sense to me, Phoebe.
- You said something about a lady? - Yes!
- What did he say? - Well, she said ...
talking pure nonsense, I do not know, like ...
Affection. We are in jail.
Try to remember and focus on what he told you.
- What the lady said? - All right.
Said.
Mental process in progress, put the ball in play.
- What the hell does that mean? - I do not know.
Phoebe, I do not know, but I remember it as if it had just passed.
I remember everything that happened to me in the last 94 minutes.
94 minutes is a number, Phoebe.
- I remember literally every second that- - Listen, just ...
Calm down.
If Mike.
You need to calm down.
I've been in this police station. Mike ...
since you were 22 years old.
Your freedom is like ...
Michael Jordan's nonsense. Because you never saw more than ...
a couple of hours?
But tonight?
Come and kill these people.
They attacked, had to defend himself.
- Forgiveness? - What would I do?
Are you his girlfriend, his mother, housekeeper?
Does your landlady?
Now is your lawyer? Why what he happened?
I think this happened.
- Mike. - I did not want to.
You wanted?
Two men are dead Mike.
No way out this time.
What the hell is that?
What?
Lock him!
We have a problem.
- What is the problem? - I do not know Phoebe, just get moving.
Wait.
What happens there?
Just wait.
All outside lights are off.
Radio, internet, phone.
What the hell is that?
Mike!
Care.
Move, move!
Come on!
Everybody down!
Phoebe Duck! Go!
Phoebe left the weapon.
Let's go!
Get out of here!
Come on.
Just a moment!
- Hello dear. - Why you have locked Liman?
Why have men in costume as if they aliens?
- What are you doing? - A mad dog is loose ...
- A real old whore. - Yes you have Adrian class.
The activaste, now two of my best men are dead.
I know why you're here, do not mess with my operation.
Your operation is murder.
It is the last time we talked.
I'm going down Yates, do you understand me?
That's not much for a middle-aged woman with ...
What is a mobile phone? You can not touch me. All right.
You can not just hang me?
Please tell me that not hung.
Phoebe, where are we going?
We go! We will leave the damn city!
I can not leave the city, you know.
They had never before tried to kill you ...
I never had that motivation. So...
Well, where are you going?
- Damn! - Look, I'll take my car ...
- And I will go to the house of Rosa. - Than?
- Than? - You want to get high now?
- Mike? - I do not want. Do not!
Rose has weapons and stuff. Yes?
And he can help us. And I'm still handcuffed.
You're in no position to make plans now.
Really? Who else? The cops are all dead.
The guy in the cell.
You pointed the gun and you said ... Weapon?
Well, I recognize that now, it is like out of mind, sorry.
Is someone trying to kill you, do not put yourself as:
What do you want to talk about?
Well, you're right. Sorry Sorry.
Just let me scream, okay?
- I'm not starting to scare. - You are.
We should try to solve and to do!
Are you okay. I'm fine.
Well, we're on our way. Yes?
And nothing happened. I promise.
Just go to my car.
Damn!
That made those guys. Demons.
All right.
Take my car.
Unknown.
Hello.
I'm in Liman, I activated Howell.
Than?
Yates and their agents are in town.
Howell tried to save and end this operation.
But something is not right. I am facing the sheriff's station ...
- And is burned. - I do not get it.
- Because you ... you should not? - Listen me.
- I need weapons. - OMG.
The operation is clean, I will send coordinates to thank me.
And I want to know where the hell Yates brings to the subject of this operation.
The procedure must be quick and quiet.
This is nonsense.
Well, sorry, I have to hang up.
- I can not, I can not. - No !, not.
Do not hang up, do not hang up.
I'm locked in the city, and I caught like a rat ...
and he will kill me.
Please Petey need you.
Very good. Here we go.
You do not make any noise. You are very quiet.
Yes, I am silent.
I am like...
I think I'm in a "allergic shock".
Try to calm down.
I try to think of good things but ...
Phoebe can not remember anything, like you never ...
I not remember having gone to school.
- Honey, do not think about that. - I went to school?
We talk sometimes my parents?
Do we walk from here and see what happens along the way?
- Yeah. - Come on.
- Fuck. - Than?
What if I'm like ...
A robot?
With gigabytes of memory reloaded.
Scheduled to fight and kill people.
Honey, you're not a robot.
What biological engineering?
- Maybe I am. - Mike.
Yes.
- You're not a robot. - How do you know it?
- There are strange things in my head. - I know. I know honey.
You know the golden M-1?
It is a type of tank.
It's like a bus.
50 kinds of tanks, when I learned of tanks?
I did not do it.
I know nothing of tanks, guns or bombs.
But now suddenly all of tanks and weapons and-
Hold it!
- Mike almost shot you! - Rose.
- What are you doing here? - Can we move on?
No no no! Come on, métanse, métanse now, man!
How to come out at night? Is the disease from monkeys?
Let métanse.
What the hell?
What the hell is all this?
Mr. Yates!
I said are discrete, covering all!
Do not put a fortress in the parking lot!
Lord, this is ...
Where are the troops?
Do you have a truck sitting in the dark?
- Lord isolate. - Well, you're right.
Thank you.
Laugher.
What happened to you? I thought you were not here.
We found the sheriff's station.
Did you see it not? What Howell?
He knocked the teeth.
But I recovered.
We just want to be a couple of hours because things are ...
I do not know, very dangerous now.
Yes, and why you come with us! Why did not you stay at home?
You say crazy, do crazy things, and here comes a madman.
I do not know what you do here. You know what I say?
Rose do not know, we just wanted to be safe.
Safe from what? Wait. Why do you think you're dangerous?
I did that before because:
- Those that? - Monkeys, monkeys!
And what you want to be safe?
Why do you say want to be safe?
Rose ... What Mike?
Together forever, man.
If the house is great, man!
My black, these are Mike and Phoebe.
- Wait ... - How are you?
Jinx ¿not? You were first as 3 weeks to injury.
Than? We did the best football team.
You did not even tell me? Fuck.
Now they have fantasies of football. You ignoring Rose, from what you say.
I guess that Rose should be alone. Guys.
You can come to football.
That does not make me feel any better, nobody asked you shit.
How rude.
Sorry, but it goes with conspiracies tonight.
Sorry. Can I ask what the monkeys?
- And gas mask? - Have not you heard?
The government has the city under fire.
There is a kind of disease that is dominating this shit.
- I'm sorry? - Than? Watch the TV!
Watch TV watching this shit.
Do you see what I say happens?
The disease has been described as a supertifus, began this afternoon.
The bridge of the city is closed to enter or leave the city.
What do you say? What did I say?
- Not ... - "Two individuals ..."
It can not be real.
If you have knowledge of his whereabouts ...
contact authorities immediately.
This is not right.
It is very contagious, stay away under any circumstances.
Official Lasseter reported that Victoria is responsible for the operation.
What do you do in the damn television, Mike?
By the inappropriate contact with several test monkeys.
- Are you involved in this? - That's the woman I'm talking about?
- Yes! - Than?
What do you know damn monkeys, man?
Calm down.
What has it easy?
I fucking answers now!
No no no!
Okay Rose, listen.
Things do not mean what you think.
This will sound silly ...
Call 1-304-1-32-01-98.
Something very strange happened to me tonight, okay?
I do not know what happens, I have killed people. Yes?
There is a possibility that I'm a robot.
Damn! You damn virus.
No Rose, stop.
- You must be quarantined, Mike. - Rose do not do that.
Back, stay away. You must be quarantined motherfucker!
- Heavens! - Do not!
How did you slut!
Rose, sorry.
Rose Well, whatever you do do not call that number of TV?
Do you think the government call?
You think you do not want them here?
- Can we talk about this, okay? - No. Mike, no.
I will not listen!
All right.
- Hey Rose. - Yes.
You can probably break that lock.
- Do not. - All right.
What place.
¿Phoebe. You think you can have this virus?
Than...? Does this false history of the disease from monkeys?
How do you know to be false?
I met this woman.
I do not feel bad?
Do you feel sick?
Not me...
I feel great.
PSYCHOTIC PARTICULAR, MAY ARM
POLICE HUNT ESPAPA CRAZY
ILL MURDERS
Mental Patient Disappears facilities.
Oh my God.
Hello.
Hello Petey.
Why I heard a drone supply come from?
You understand that going against the efforts of a CIA operation.
¿Acting against national security?
What do we call that Petey?
When acting against the interests of country, is treason?
Acláramelo because I forgot.
What is the penalty for treason?
Do you carry out and shoot you in the fucking head?
I'm aware that you are faithful to Lasseter.
Do not do more. You will never operate. Got it?
Thank you for things, I will find it now ...
but first you have to make this public, call Krueger ...
I can not believe this Yates using mental patients for this.
I must inform you that it is my duty not to disclose this operation.
Duty? What?
We need for this, is completely -
If you do this operation you make public betrayal on betrayal ...
- from United States. - No, Petey.
- Peter. - I'm sorry.
Petey!
I can not help more.
Damn!
Phoebe, what are you doing?
I am seeking an escape.
Phoebe, stop, do not think we do that, okay?
We must wait here, Rose is good guy.
He's just sensible.
Honey, I'm not thinking ill of you sold the drugs.
Already they located Howell?
It's in his friend's house.
Well, come on then. Understood?
¿Put Newman, Laugher and Burger, all ready?
- Yes sir! - Actívenlo and ...
I'll call air support.
No further incidents.
No more mistakes.
Clean and sweep!
- Dammit! - You know you're doing?
I'll go ahead and see if I get to the other room.
Just a moment.
This is not the right time.
- That I can not move. - I do not think that .
What's up?
Oh, hell!
Phoebe! Move!
Fuck.
Grab the gun and let's go.
Let's go!
Affection?
Affection? Come here, come.
We awake. Come on.
You should be awake. Yes?
That crap will make you feel very tired. You'll help a little.
- Just stay awake, okay? - I feel sleepy.
Do not sleep! Do not sleep!
Honey, if you sleep you die. Sleep and die.
So it works. Close your senses one by one.
Keep your eyes open. Open your damn eyes.
Affection. Affection?
Affection?
Honey awake. Wake up wake up. Yes?
No !, what whores ... no!
What with Chip and brick!
Apollo with the ape, I love it, I love it ...
if you die. You lose ... I love you.
Honey, please.
Mike, wake up.
I love you.
All right?
Mike, I like this place.
I love you.
A new beginning.
Far from everyone.
Just you and me.
You are free.
Far from all this.
I love you.
All right.
Interview number 13985.
Mike!
I love you.
All right.
Up. Breathe.
Up. Wake up.
Mike. Breathe!
It's okay.
How did you know what was the gas?
No, no, what?
- How did you know what was the gas? - I do not know what happens.
But listen.
Affection.
Mike.
I do not know what happens.
But I know that about me, okay?
- Just listen. - Well, tell me.
- This does not make sense now. - What's up? Tell me.
I...
I'm your supervisor.
You were assigned me five years ago.
Does my supervisor?
Please understand, I ...
I am of the CIA, yes?
- But. - What about you?
Listen to me, okay. - Phoebe.
- I try to tell you this for a long time. - Are not you my girlfriend?
Of course I'm your girlfriend! Affection.
So I say, no ...
To please, I can not even look at you .. I must go.
Mike!
Mike, let me explain.
- Mike. - Do not.
- Leave me alone. - Open the door, Mike!
Leave me alone!
Oh, hell.
No, let me, let me, let me go.
Well, I know something.
I am real?
Yeah, you're real.
Are your parents really dead?
Is everything you told me is a lie?
- Not everything is a lie. - Please do not use that voice with me.
- No. - I was in love with you.
I'm in love with you, and who is not you?
- Stop it, Mike! - Stop mourn falsely ...
to cover all this ...
and leave my emotions, just stop mourn.
Please stop it.
Hears! Stop! Yes? Damn! Stop!
I will not lie anymore.
Give me one more chance to show you that you do not lie, right?
Clear.
- No, Mike. - Phoebe, get out of my car.
- I can not. - Get out of my car! Yes?
- Get out of my car! - It's my damn car!
Just get out of the car!
Phoebe!
How to survive a lie?
You're lucky.
No, no ...
Phoebe! Phoebe!
! Phoebe!
I want to do something very bad.
Phoebe ...
Fuck.
Oh, hell! what is that?
Is gasoline?
Yes!
Do not! Hell, no.
Oh, hell!
Come on, man.
I hate you man!
I also hate you man!
I wanted to tell you something.
Hey, wake up.
Hears. Wake up!
I said I wanted to say something.
Look!
Mike. Mike!
Mr!
God, but it is the Cinderella 2010.
Yates. What are you doing here?
I am a professional.
Who is running this operation?
Since when desktop like you guys are in the field?
Because it's a problem, I was in the dark five years, can not I?
Do you have an authorization from this?
Where is Krueger?
Phoebe Silver, which left the program ...
and return here. Will you question my operation?
I read your file!
You have no secrets from me.
Your boyfriend is not real.
We created it.
Sorry if you finished working on "Taco Bell".
It's probably why you ruined your life.
I guess so.
Look what I am now in charge of a major operation.
And look where you are.
Under arrest for insubordination and waiting.
And I get a promotion.
Your pathetic boyfriend will be neutralized.
It's okay.
Mike.
Do you recognize me?
You know my name?
Are you the wife of the market?
Yes.
But you know who I am?
Are you my mother?
Do not.
- No no no. - Do not!
I'm not going anywhere until you tell me about me.
Look...
when you were eighteen, I saw you.
That was the first time I met you.
He is recruiting people for a program called Wiseman.
Basically the volunteers gave extra abilities.
And I offered the opportunity to volunteer.
¿Volunteer for what?
To be ... To be an experiment.
An experiment?
Yes.
That was a mistake.
No, Mike, you ran.
All others were failures but not you.
You succeeded.
But I was going crazy.
Turned away all crazy.
The risks were horrible and very large.
So I closed it and gave them a new life ...
a new identity.
- To you you started here. - Yes.
So my memories erased ...
You fucked my head.
And you left me here.
With a fake girlfriend.
No, Mike, please.
This is not who you are.
You can not leave town.
Phobias.
- We did that to protect you. - Protect me?
Yes.
And the guys trying to kill me?
Hears! You're the woman on TV!
Hello.
Fucked monkeys.
Than?
Mike, where are you going?
Mr...
Howell still alive.
He was seen at a gas station. For the Chesnut Street.
Damn!
Hello.
Hello Petey.
I need a drone in the sky in less than an hour.
Call me when you come into my airspace.
So you'll fly a village full of civilians?
- I have to do it. - To capture a single guy?
So is!
Phoebe.
This is over.
It's okay.
Come on! Back to work!
Dron, 3.5 off in parallel on the road.
He again watching ...
Two subjects east along the perimeter.
You will return to the house.
It will not return to the house.
Mike can be a bit slow at times ...
but it's not a fucking idiot.
Mike, I can not let you get back to your house.
I'm going in and I'm going to sleep.
They have snipers may be there now.
Then shoot me! Please!
Why are you still here?
- I do not want you to die? - Why?
Why...
Because I care about you.
Very good. I do not care, okay?
And if I die.
I'll do it and laugh in my bed.
You can stay or you can go.
Otis, I need you and Beedle the house to view the location of Lasseter.
And Howell.
- But now.
- Thank you, now. - Yes sir!
What the hell view?
Who is Apollo Ape?
It is a monkey astronaut.
I did, and live adventures.
Mike, Phoebe is not supposed to return.
When you were on the show, she always take care of you.
While the other subjects failed ...
you had success.
She has great faith in you.
You were assigned to it ..
We were supposed to leave town and out reassigned.
She decided to stay with you.
She left everything, a whole new life.
I thought you should know that.
Lady. Lasseter
Sighting. We have them in sight.
Confirm sighting.
Requesting immediate reinforcements.
Copied. Do not let them go. ¿Colin?
- What with Howell? - Shoot the drone, come on.
Let's hit.
Agent Douglas, please confirm.
- Ready to hit. - We'll give you the position.
All right.
Oh, hell!
Very good. Stay here.
Beedle!
Target in progress. Confirmation of destruction.
Fire!
Agent Douglas confirmed.
What is wrong with you people? Throw him already!
Throw him already!
Now! Fire! Now!
Lord lose the distance of the target.
- Damn idiots! - Agent Douglas .
10, 9, 8, ...
7, 6, 5, 4 ...
Fuck!
off target.
So that was the trick.
Oh, hell.
Call.
Speaks Krueger.
Hello Mr. Krueger.
Do you have a moment?
Withdraw immediately following the protocol.
How is it that you managed all this lead?
Do not answer.
- Are you the kind that- - definitely it.
- Then I'll respond. - No, Mike.
- Hello? - Hello.
Who is it?
You first.
Are you fuck?
Listen.
- Are you Mike Howell? - Yes.
- Who you are? - The house is not ...
- Burning? - No, the house is as usual.
Very good.
What's the plan now?
I mean, do you surrender?
Well, you caught me.
I give up.
Why do not you come to me and accept my surrender?
About how Wilson?
Yes.
It's what is across the tire store is 10 minutes.
Than? If it is okay.
What happens when I see you there ...?
And do you accept the surrender, I sign something?
Your girlfriend is here.
Would you like to tell you, I love you?
I do not know.
What if I grab my gun and blow your head?
Would it be great with that?
No, it would not be great.
Did she really is with you?
Mike.
I'm sorry.
I have been honest.
I have always been sincere, even in the car.
Really?
I love you.
You can go, anywhere you want and never-
That was unfortunate.
Mike what do you do?
I'll save my girlfriend.
I'll handle this.
Now!
Get out of the fucking truck!
They know what to do.
Go Go. Fast!
Come on!
That's!
This is the time so I have trained.
This is not a trial. Yes?
This type is lethal, violent, and we should eliminate it.
This clear?
Rufus, bring it here!
¿Phoebe?
- Phoebe. - Mike!
I never meant that. That I love you and ...
Everything will be OK.
Obviously not perfect, but ...
Best.
You probably want to know.
Pcs. Two might kill him, please.
Kill him.
And this will end soon.
¿Phoebe?
Yates. Give up.
Let me go, that is all you want.
food utensils.
Go, go!
Move.
¿Phoebe?
Rufus, ends this.
Go ahead, Mike.
Salt.
I just want to talk with you.
- Now you know. - Than?
What is? What is what?
What do you say I know?
Fuck!
I am? Now?
You're pathetic, you know my boyfriend.
You'll kill you know.
You know what?
I think you want one of my tooth.
Fuck that.
Fuck!
Introduce early morning at the agency ...
I betrayed us, going behind your head.
You are scaring me.
Please, can you go?
I just want to talk.
I want to talk.
I'm sorry.
But I can not remember.
The things they did to my head.
Did they do to you and to me.
But you're better than me.
Who told you to do?
Anyone.
It must feel good.
Who is the bank now? Damn!
Enough, Laciret.
Enough!
Mike?
Home...
You want to go home?
Yes.
It's okay.
He said yes!
Come on, I could give you a fellowships
Congratulations on the cursed forest in the bloody rain ...
this is an unacceptable level.
I just wanted to say that Mr. Petey is not responsible for any ...
action in the last 24 hours.
Douglas did not know what I did with you, helping you.
Interfered directly in government operations.
As a result you caused the deaths of dozens of civilians.
That's right?
- Yes sir. - Absolutely right, sir.
Thanks to Lasseter 7 Americans are dead.
- In our operation .. - Is the operation you created though ...?
Does not have authorization?
- Is it right? - Yes sir!
But you have to understand ...
I acted by choice.
Excuse me?
I made mistakes ...
Do you know? Yes, I did.
Do I take shortcuts? Of course!
But in the end I justify what I did to fix ...
replace it with another system. And they pushed me to do so.
You'd be grateful, right?
Come on, would you be thanking you?
Yes.
All right.
Thank you.
I do not think this is necessary.
Please do not kill me.
I am your source.
When I call you to tell you what happened.
I did it out of courtesy and now regrets.
That was not my intention, but acted like a girl ...
and tried to save your puppy.
The puppy was now. And now the puppy her dead puppy ...
And the puppy what is shitting everywhere!
You have a crazy rabid puppy that kills people.
And still you need to be settled.
You understood! Right?
Yes sir!
Maybe you are looking for the way this ends well ...
and pulls out a miracle of your ass.
Because if you can not.
That will be you.
And it has its miracle Lord.
My program works.
Wiseman beat tough guys.
Mike Howell, remove 17 tough guys, one by one.
That makes it the most efficient cash we have seen in any other program.
Never.
In 60 years.
Excuse me for saying so, sir.
But saving the puppy saved ...
$ 400 million in puppies ...
and he is sitting in a cell at this time.
Are you going to kill?
Where do you want to start?
Howell agent.
Manila, Philippines, six months later.
Be right back.
According.
Hello.
They took the bait.
Is the?
When we got him.
Above all I had was this.
Fuck you!
You think you're ready?
I'm Da Wei Rao.
And they just sent a man?
An unarmed man?
Something you find funny?
I'm sorry.
I knew I could not speak Mandarin.
Antillean and Th0ravenger work.